<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>dobriak::blog on dobriak::blog </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>https://dobriak.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 22:05:07 MST</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Jenkins with a private docker registry on DC/OS</title>
      <link>https://dobriak.github.io/post/jenkins-marathonlb-dcos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 22:05:07 MST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dobriak.github.io/post/jenkins-marathonlb-dcos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this guide I will walk you through setting up your Jenkins instance to use the private docker registry we set up in the previous blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure private Docker registry on DC/OS</title>
      <link>https://dobriak.github.io/post/docker-registry-marathonlb-dcos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 16:45:12 MST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dobriak.github.io/post/docker-registry-marathonlb-dcos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a short guide on how to set up a private docker registry behind an internal marathon-lb instance all running on DC/OS. Since marathon-lb is a Layer 7 load balancer we will use it to terminate SSL for our private registry and avoid using it in insecure mode. We will use self-signed TLS certificates for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dobriak.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 16:44:40 MST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dobriak.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you need to get in touch with me, feel free to do it through LinkedIn or AngelCo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dobriak.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 16:44:33 MST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dobriak.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Julian Neytchev, and I have been making sure to turn it off and on again since 1995.
I spent the first 10 years of my career as a software developer, wrote a lot of code, and filed a lot of TPS reports. I think I still have my red stapler tucked somewhere.
Then one day in 2010 I got a job offer from the consulting arm of Red Hat looking for someone to work on reference architecture design and development for one of their biggest clients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

